Finding Aid to the Save the Redwoods League photograph collection. 1885-2014
The Bancroft Library
- Series 1: Vertical Files., 1897-2014; cartons 1-8; A box 1; AX box 1, folders 1-20; B box 1, folders 1-15, 17-18; C box 1; D folder 1; F folder 1; H folder 1; NEG boxes 1-5; NEG(gl) boxes 1, 3, 8, 9; NNEG boxes 1-6
  - Drury, Newton B., 1920-1973; 2 folders (Carton 2)
    - Presentation to Governor Ronald Reagan of California of $7 million for Pepperwood Grove addition to Humboldt Redwoods State Park., March 13, 1968; BANC PIC 2006.030--PIC; 1 photograph (Carton 2)
      Duplicate copy folder: Reagan, Ronald, at presentation of funds for Pepperwood.
      This material was selectively digitized from a larger resource or collection. From folder: Drury, Newton
      Conservation of natural resources -- California
  - Enduring Giants. (Carton 2)
    Photographs of Calaveras Big Trees State Park used in publication. All are copy prints of images from the late 1800s and early 1900s.
  - Ericson (A.W. Ericson) photographs of scenes in the California redwoods., circa 1880s; Ericson, A. W. (Augustus William) (Ax box 1, Folder 3-6)
    12 albumen photographic prints on cardboard mounts. From photographer's series: Scenes in the California Redwoods, and Scenes in the Redwoods, Humboldt County.
  - Ersa of the Red Trees production., 1922-1927 (Carton 2)
    Performance in the redwoods directed by Garnet Holme. Includes 1927 production: Romance of the Redwoods. Photographs by Lindley Eddy.
  - Etchings of the Big Trees of California., 1960 (Carton 2)
    Publication of etchings by Alec Stern.
  - Eureka, Humboldt County., 1934-circa 1960? undated (Carton 2)
    Includes City Hall and Carson House (also known as the Ingomar Club) in the city of Eureka.
    1 matching copy negative removed to NEG box 3. 2 matching negatives removed to NNEG box 3. 1 matching negative removed to NNEG box 2
  - Exhibits., 1934-1966 (Carton 2)
    Text relating to, and photographs of, redwood related exhibits and displays. Bulk are Save-the-Redwoods League exhibits. Includes planting of a sequoia tree at the Seattle World's Fair, Garden Club of America exhibit, and displays at Big Basin State Park.
  - Exhibits -- Golden Gate International Exhibition., 1939 (Carton 2)
    Snapshots of the California State Park Commission and Save-the-Redwoods League outdoor exhibit on the south side of the Philippine Building.
  - Fish illustration. (Carton 2)
    Image of a fish mounted on board. Appears to be from a rubber stamp.
  - Flora of the redwood region (black and white)., 1930-1933, undated; 2 folders (Carton 2)
    Many images are duplicated in the notebook album, "Native Trees, Shrubs & Flowers of the Redwood Region." Includes snow in redwoods regions. Includes photographs by Lawton, Russell Angel, Martin and Malcolm Brode.
    2 matching negatives removed to NEG box 1. 6 matching negatives removed to NNEG box 3. 2 related negatives of flowers removed to NNEG box 2.
  - Flora of the redwood region (color)., 1968-1977, undated (Carton 2)
    2 matching color transparencies removed to NEG box 3.
  - Flora of the redwood region -- Native Trees, Shrubs and Flowers of the Redwood Region., circa 1930s (Carton 2)
    Notebook type album.
    Includes photographs by Lawton, Russell Angel, Martin and Malcolm Brode.
  - Flora of the redwood region -- Rhododendron., 1936, undated (Carton 2)
    Includes photographs by Lawton, George E. Stone and Patterson.
    5 matching color transparencies removed to NEG box 3. 3 related negatives removed to NNEG box 2.
  - Forest of Nisene Marks State Park., 1980-06-07 (Carton 2)
    Snapshots of a Save-the-Redwoods League directors field trip to this park.
  - Forest of Nisene Marks State Park, oversize., circa 1980? (D folder 1)
  - Fort Ross., 1989 (Carton 2)
    Includes photographs by Ron Hanshew.
    22 matching 35mm negatives removed to NEG box 2.
  - Gerstung photographs of Mendocino and Sonoma Counties., 1971-1991 (Caarton 2)
    Photographs by Eric Gerstung. Includes Albion River Estuary, coast at DeVilbiss Ranch, Gualala River Estuary and redwood grove owned by Gualala Redwoods Company.
  - Gills, Curtis E., photographer., 1901 (Carton 2)
    Copy print of "Redwoods in California." Men posed at a redwood tree during logging. Folder contains 1 item.
  - Grant Ranch, Santa Clara County., 1932-1981 (Carton 2)
    Grant Ranch and of the transfer of the Ranch to the Santa Clara County. Includes view of Lick Observatory on hill top, and some documents.
    20 matching copy negatives removed to NEG box 1.
  - Gray Whale Ranch, Wilder Ranch State Park -- Garrison photographs., April 26, 2000 (Carton 2)
    Snapshots by Holly Garrison.
    14 matching 35mm negatives removed to NEG box 2. 1 photo CD removed to NEG box 1.
  - Gray Whale Ranch, Wilder Ranch State Park -- Shaver photographs., Octoner 22, 1998 (Carton 2)
    Snapshots by Mack Shaver.
    66 matching and related 35mm negatives removed to NEG box 2.
  - Grizzly Creek Redwoods State Park (Humboldt County)., 1928-1979, undated (Carton 2)
    Includes Cheatham Grove, the Van Duzen River, map of redwood groves along the Van Duzen River, map of Grizzly Creek Redwoods State Park and map of proposed acquisition with locations of photographs by David Swanlund.
    Includes photographs by Drury and David Swanlund.
    4 matching negatives removed to NEG box 1.
  - Grizzly Creek Redwoods State Park -- 65-500., 1996 (Carton 2)
  - Grizzly Creek Redwoods State Park -- 68-500., 1968 (Carton 2)
    Includes photographs by David Swanlund.
  - Grizzly Creek Redwoods State Park -- 69-500., 1969 (Carton 2)
  - Grizzly Creek Redwoods State Park -- 71-500., 1971 (Carton 2)
  - Grizzly Creek Redwoods State Park -- 73-500., 1973 (Carton 2)
  - Grove benches, plaques, signs and inscriptions., 1922-1964, undated (Carton 2)
    Includes community bonfire benches at Prairie Creek Grove, boulder for Toumey Grove marker, Grant Grove marker, sign for Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park and US Forest Service campground signs.
    5 negatives (1 matching and 4 related) removed to NEG box 1. 23 related negatives of benches and plaques in Prairie Creek removed to NEG box 2. 9 related negatives of markers for Grant Grove, California Federation of Women's Club Grove and James W. Toumey Grove removed to NNEG box 2.
  - Grove of the Old Trees, Sonoma County., 2001? (Carton 2)
    Formerly Van Alstyne Grove. All are digital prints.
  - Gutteridge., 1958-1968 (Carton 2)
    Descriptive list of photograph taken by John E. Gutteridge in Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park, July 1959. Includes a map of the groves. Does not include photographs.
  - Haid's Flower Shop, Santa Ana, Calif., March 1938 (Carton 2)
    Flower shop built around a redwood tree.
    Save-the-Redwoods League numbers 14,000-14,002.
    4 matching negatives removed to NNEG box 3.
  - Hammarskjold, Dag, memorial service at Muir Woods., April 4, 1965 (Carton 2)
    Ceremony commemorating the establishment of the Dag Hammarskjold Memorial Grove on Avenue of the Giants. Event held in Muir Woods.
  - Hartsook tree planting., 2005? (Carton 2)
    CD with digital copy of image removed to NEG box 1.
  - Hawks property in Section 24., 1967 (Carton 2)
    Correspondence, map and snapshots related to parcels of land probably in or near Humboldt Redwoods State Park.
  - Hendy Woods State Park (Mendocino County)., 1927-1992, undated (Carton 2)
    Includes Hendy Grove and Navarro River.
    Includes photographs by Saunders and David Swanlund.
    3 copy negatives (2 matching and 1 related) removed to NEG box 1.
  - Hendy Woods State Park, oversize., 4 photographs (B box 1, Folder 2)
    Panoramas of Hendy Grove, by Saunders Foto, Ukiah, Cal. 2 are copies.
  - Hendy Woods State Park, oversize., 1928?; 4 photographs (H folder 1)
    Panoramic landscapes of pastures and redwood trees, and redwood groves at Hendy Tract, Hendy Woods and Hendy Grove. 2 are copies.
    Photographs by Saunders Foto, Ukiah, Calif.
  - Hendy Woods State Park -- 83-500., 1983 (Carton 2)
  - Henry Cowell Redwoods State Park (Santa Cruz County)., 1920s-1981 (Carton 2)
    Includes Fenton, Santa Cruz Grove, Welch's Big Tree Grove, dining room among the redwood trees and largest card receiver in the world.
    Park also referred to as Santa Cruz Big Trees.
    Photographs by W.H. Sherer and Philip McFaul.
  - Hooker Oak, Birdwell Park., 1928 (Carton 2)
    1 related negative removed to NNEG box 2.
  - Hoover, Herbert., 1928- (Carton 2)
    Hoover camp at Bull Creek, Humboldt Redwoods State Park and Herbert Hoover at the Big Tree in Stout Grove, Jedediah Smith Redwoods State Park.
    Photo numbers Humboldt 29-01 thru 29-08.
    1 matching copy negative removed to NEG box 1
  - Humboldt County., circa 1906-1968 (Carton 2)
    Miscellaneous and unidentified locations in Humboldt County, some of which are along Avenue of the Giants or an unidentified highway. Includes coastal scenes, area in and near Scotia, Carson Woods, Mad River and Humboldt-Del Norte County line.
    Includes photographs by Gabriel Moulin, Newton B. Drury, Emerson Knight, H.W. Shepherd, Obert's Photoshop, and Martin Studio.
    1 matching negative removed to NEG box 1. 7 related negatives (1 of Bishop Pine Lodge near Trinidad, 6 of Hansen-Carothers property) removed to NNEG box 3. 1 matching negative removed to NNEG box 2.
  - Humboldt County, oversize., 1928; 2 photographs (Ax box 1, Folder 7)
    Mystery of the Forest area at Camp Grant, by H.S. Lawton (2 copies).
  - Humboldt County, oversize., 2 photographs (G folder 1)
    "The California Redwoods," panoramic landscape of redwood forest with dirt road and man (2 copies). Written on back: Humboldt redwoods near Dyerville.
  - Humboldt County, oversize., 1 photograph (H folder 1)
    "On the Redwood Highway, Humboldt Co., California," panoramic landscape of redwood forest with dirt road. Photograph by Freeman Art Co., Eureka, Calif. (number 1009).
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park (Humboldt County)., 1919-1972; 2 folders (Carton 2)
    Includes Dyerville Bridge; Mystery of the Forest, Frederic Saltonstall Gould Grove; Big Tree in Kraus Grove; Secretary of the Interior Hubert Work and party in Bull Creek Flat, 1925; Semi-Centennial ceremony of Save-the-Redwoods; Children's Forest; Edith Harwood Keck Grove; Day W. Symmes Gove.
    Includes photographs by Moulin Studios, Howard King and David Swanlund.
    Photo numbers Humboldt 19-01 thru 19-12.
    3 matching negatives removed to NEG box 1. 1 matching negative removed to NNEG box 3 (4x5). 5 negatives (1 matching and 4 related) removed to NNEG box 2 (5x7). 4 matching negatives removed to NNEG box 4 (8x10). 1 matching lantern slide removed to NEG(gl) box 8.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park, oversize., 1921?-circa 1960; 8 photographs and 2 maps (Ax box 1, Folder 8)
    Bolling Grove and monument; Mrs. Kate Felton in Felton Grove, photograph by Drury; large maple overhanging river at edge of Federation Grove, photograph by Russell Angel; Avenue of the Giants, photographs by Moulin Studios; Bull Creek-Dyerville Forest (Rockefeller Forest) dedication in 1931; Rockefeller Forest area, photograph by Moulin Studios; map of proposed Redwood Park vicinity, Bull Creek-Dyerville (2 copies).
    1 matching negative removed to NNEG box 2.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park, oversize., circa 1950?; 5 photographs (B box 1, Folder 3)
    Felton Grove monument, photograph by Lawton (3 copies). Wentworth Grove, Avenue of the Giants and Daly Grove, photographs by John E. Gutteridge (F-6, H-3).
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park, oversize., 1 photograph (C box 1, Folder 4)
    Founders Tree. Photograph by Moulin (number 15372).
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park, oversize., August 24, 1924; 3 photographs (G folder 1)
    "Dedication of Franklin K. Lane Memorial Redwoods," panorama of people in a redwood grove. Photograph by Freeman Art Co., Eureka, Calif. Duplicate filed in oversize H.
    "The California Redwoods," panoramic landscape of redwood forest with dirt road and man. (2 copies), written verso: Humboldt redwoods near Dyerville.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park, oversize., 1924, undated; 2 photographs (H folder 1)
    "Lane Grove, Kettintelbe," panoramic landscape of redwood forest with dirt road near Phillipsville, Humboldt County, Calif.
    "Dedication of the Franklin K. Lane Memorial Redwood Grove, August 24, 1924." Photograph by Freeman Art Co. Duplicate filed as oversize G.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Aerial views., 1956, 1966 (Carton 2)
    Numbers HC-66, 26A-39 to 34A-29.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Aerial views, oversize., 1963; 11 photographs (B box 1, Folder 4)
    Humboldt Redwoods State Park area, including Avenue of the Giants, Pepperwood Barkull Property. Similar to aerial photographs in folder: Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Aerial views.
    Numbered HC-S-2-3 19-50 to HC-S-2-3 25A-46.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Arcata Redwood Company lands., 1964-1965 (Carton 2)
    Includes aerial views of clear-cut land.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Avenue of the Giants., 1935-1977; 2 folders (Carton 2)
    Includes photo numbers Humboldt 33-01 thru 33-16 and 32-17 thru 32-45. See also Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Highway
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Avenue of the Giants -- Aerial photographs., 1966 (Carton 2)
    Photographs by John Summerly.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Avenue of the Giants -- Dedication., August 27, 1960 (Carton 2)
    Includes Governor Edmund G. Brown.
    Photo numbers Humboldt 26-01 thru 26-13.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Avenue of the Giants -- Freeway construction., 1963-1964 (Carton 2)
    Photographs by Martin Litton and David Swanlund.
    Photo numbers Humboldt 27-01 thru 27-08.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Avenue of the Giants -- Gutteridge photographs., 1956 (Carton 2)
    Photographs by John E. Gutteridge. Includes Mailliard Grove, Connick Grove, Starr Grove and Wentworth Grove.
    Photo numbers Humboldt 32-01 thru 32-29.
    59 negatives (7 matching and 52 related) removed to NEG box 1.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Avenue of the Giants -- Swanlund photographs., September 1962; 2 folders (Carton 3)
    Photo numbers Humboldt 30-01 thru 30-26.
    - Family at Avenue of the Giants, Humboldt Redwoods State Park., September 1962; Swanlund, David; BANC PIC 2006.030--PIC; 1 photograph (Carton 3)
      Includes camper in the background.
      Photograph 37.
      This material was selectively digitized from a larger resource or collection. From folder: Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Avenue of the Giants -- Swanlund photographs (1 of 2).
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Barkdull-Holmes Ranch., 1970? (Carton 3)
    Photo number Humboldt 23-01.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bolling Grove., 1921 (Carton 3)
    Includes the dedication of the grove.
    Photo numbers Humboldt 28-01. See also Humboldt Redwoods State Park, oversize AX.
    3 matching copy negatives removed to NEG box 1. 3 matching negatives removed to NNEG box 3.
    - Group of men standing next to the Bolling Grove memorial plaque at the dedication of the grove., August 6, 1921; BANC PIC 2006.030--PIC; 1 photograph (Carton 3)
      This material was selectively digitized from a larger resource or collection. From folder: Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bolling Grove.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bolling Grove, oversize., August 6, 1921; 2 photographs (C box 1, Folder 3)
    Group portraits of men at dedication of grove. Modern duplicates of photographs in folder: Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bolling Grove.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bull Creek., circa 1920s-1969; 3 folders (Carton 3)
    Bull Creek and Bull Creek Flat. Includes Hoover camp; dedication ceremony; Mr. and Mrs. Gilbert Grosvenor, Mr. and Mrs. Newton B. Drury, and Mr. Wright in front of Giant Tree; Glen Thompson, first ranger, next to the Flat Iron Tree; Eel River; damage from 1964 flood.
    Includes photographs by H.C. Tibbitts, Freeman Art Company, Martin Studio, Moulin, H.S. Lawton, Newton B. Drury, L.C. Merriam, Philip Hyde, David Swanlund, Howard King and Gregory Thomas.
    See also Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Rockefeller Forest. Includes photo numbers Humboldt 35-01 thru 35-48.
    6 matching negatives removed to NEG box 1. 2 matching negatives removed to NNEG box 4.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bull Creek, oversize., 1954? undated; 3 photographs (Ax box 1, Folder 9)
    Bull Creek Watershed map comparing logging from 1947-1954 (2 copies). Bull Creek Flat.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bull Creek, oversize., 1911-1962; 3 photographs (B box 1, Folder 5)
    Mouth of Bull Creek, by Freeman Art Company. Bull Creek at Upper Bull Creek, by H.C. Tibbitts. Panoramic view of Bull Creek from Johnson Prairie, by Tryner.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bull Creek -- Aerial views., 1932-1966 (Carton 3)
    Bull Creek watershed. Includes bird's-eye views from mountain top.
    Includes photographs by Fairchild Aerial Surveys, Moulin Studios and David Swanlund.
    Photo numbers Humboldt 25-01 thru 25-14.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bull Creek -- Erosion and sedimentation., 1957-1972 (Carton 3)
    Includes Blue Slide above Bull Creek.
    Includes photographs by Moulin Studios, Alexander Lowry and Howard King.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bull Creek -- Lowdermilk Study., October 1961 (Carton 3)
    Study on erosion. Photographs by Walter C. Lowdermilk.
    Photo numbers Humboldt 17-01 thru 17-13.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bull Creek -- Lowdermilk Study I., October 1961 (Carton 3)
    Photo numbers Humboldt 17-I-01 thru 17-I-17.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bull Creek -- Lowdermilk Study II., October 1961 (Carton 3)
    Photo numbers Humboldt 17-II-01 thru 17-II-18.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bull Creek -- Lowdermilk Study III., October 1961 (Carton 3)
    Photo numbers Humboldt 17-III-01 thru 17-III-07.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bull Creek -- Lowdermilk Study -- Miscellaneous., October 1961 (Carton 3)
    Miscellaneous erosion and sedimentation photographs. Photographs by Walter C. Lowdermilk.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bull Creek -- Metcalf photograph., 1922 (Carton 3)
    "In the Bull Creek Flat, Rockefeller Forest." Richard F. Hammatt leaning against tree. Photograph by Woodbridge Metcalf. Includes a brochure.
    Photo numbers Humboldt 33-01.
    2 matching copy negatives (copies of same image) removed to NEG box 1 and NNEG box 2.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bull Creek -- Standish and Hickey lands., 1920s (Carton 3)
    5000 acres on Bull Creek.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Bull Creek -- Visit., 1963 (Carton 3)
    Save-the-Redwoods League officers visiting Bull Creek. Includes Newton B. Drury, Aubrey Johnson, Bob Curless, Corky Aden, T.A. Greig, Ralph W. Chaney and Gene Kincaid.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Canoe Creek., 1932-2003 (Carton 3)
    Includes Canoe Creek fire photographs by Ian Condon.
    6 negatives of fire (5 matching and 1 related) removed to NEG box 2.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Children's Forest., 6 photographs (Ax box 1, Folder 10)
    2 photographs by Newton B. Drury, 4 photographs by Russell Angel.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Coombs Property., 1972 (Carton 3)
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park – Connick photographs of Blair and Pioneers Groves., June 11, 1938 (Carton 3)
    Snapshots, by Robert Connick, of trees cut in the Samuel, Abigail B. and William S. Blair Grove and The Pioneers Grove.
    5 matching negatives removed to NNEG box 3. 1 matching copy negative removed to NEG box 1.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Cuneo Creek., 1955-1965 (Carton 3)
    Photo numbers Humboldt 1-01 thru 1-12.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Dyerville., 1919-1960
    Area around Dyerville/Dyerville Flats, in or near the park. Includes the Lizard Tree.
    Includes photographs by William Schoeb, Mason, and H.C. Tibbitts.
    1 related copy negative removed to NEG box 1. 2 matching negatives removed to NNEG box 3 (4x5). 4 related negatives removed to NNEG box 2 (5x7). 2 related negatives removed to NNEG box 4 (8x10).
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Dyerville, oversize., 3 photographs (G folder 1)
    "North Dyerville Flat." Panoramic landscape of redwood forest with dirt road, Humboldt County, Calif. (3 copies, 1 has a different cropping). Photograph by Freeman Art Co., Eureka, Calif.
    Title from back of photo.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Dyerville Giant., circa 1987 (Carton 3)
    Includes an oversize postcard.
    4 color transparencies (2 matching and 2 related) removed to NEG box 3.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Eel River., 1924-1977 (Carton 3)
    Includes South Fork of Eel River, flood damage, California Federation of Women's Club Grove.
    Includes photographs by Gordon Lord, Howard King, David Swanlund.
    Photo numbers Humboldt 13-01 thru 13-17.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Eel River -- Aerial views., 1966-1968 (Carton 3)
    Includes Federation Grove.
    Includes photographs by David Swanlund and Howard King.
    Photo numbers Humboldt 12-01 thru 12-11.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Founders Tree, 1931-1946 (Carton 3)
    Includes dedication of the Founders Tree.
    Includes photographs by J.C. Merriam, Gabriel Moulin and Gordon Lord.
    1 matching negative removed to NNEG box 2. 3 negatives (1 matching and 2 related) removed to NEG(gl) box 3. 2 related 8x10 glass negatives removed to NEG(gl) box 9.
    - Founders Tree dedication, Dyerville, Humboldt Redwoods State Park., September 15, 1931; BANC PIC 2006.030--NNEG; 1 photograph (Nneg box 4)
      Photograph by Martin. Numbered: 5056. This material was selectively digitized from a larger resource or collection. Print available in folder: Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Founders Tree.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Garden Club of America Grove., circa 1930, 1977 (Carton 3)
    Includes photographs by Newton B. Drury, Gabriel Moulin, Russell Angel and Howard King.
    1 related negative of large birds in a nest removed to NEG box 1.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Grate Property., March 1970 (Carton 3)
    Photo numbers Humboldt 14-01 thru 14-17.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Grove photographs by Swanlund, David., February 1968 (Carton 3)
    Includes Groves H-1, H-2, H-3, H-4, H-5, H-7, H-8, H-10, H-12, H-13, H-14, H-15, H-21, H-22, H-23, H-27, H-45, H-46, H-49 7, H-48, H-49, and old Grove 9 along the Avenue of the Giants extension.
    Photographs formerly housed in a notebook.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Highway., 1938-1968 (Carton 3)
    Redwood Highway along US Route 101. Includes construction, George M. Leatherwood Bridge and aerial views.
    Includes photographs by Moulin Studios, David Swanlund and Tryner.
    Photo numbers Humboldt 8-01 thru 8-16.
    2 matching copy negatives removed to NEG box 1.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Highway, oversize., May 1959; 1 photograph (C box 1, Folder 4)
    View looking south, completed U.S. Highway 101/Redwood Highway. George M. Leatherwood Bridge over the South Fork of the Eel River in center. Division of Highways photograph.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Highway -- Tree removal., 1938 (Carton 3)
    Letter and photographs from the US Department of the Interior, National Park Service regarding tree removal along the right-of-way on the Redwood Highway.
    Photographs labeled C-230 to C-243.
  - Humboldt Redwoods State Park -- Highway survey, Schoeb photographs., 1937; 3 folders (Carton 3)
    Bulk are of Dyerville-Englewood Tract.
    Save-the Redwoods League numbers 5255-5256. Also see album: Views of State Highway U.S. 101 Humboldt Redwoods State Park Illustrating Problems in Highway Widening and Re-Alignment.